

MAMISOA HYACINTHE

Application Developer - Automation Engineer -Electrician

+971 55 748 7854



mamisoa.hyacinthe90@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

A business application developer (WEB, Mobile, Desktop) with 10 years of experience in .NET C#, PHP, JAVA, JavaScript, and TypeScript, I stand out for my leadership and communication skills. My experience has also taught me to constantly adapt, as the IT industry is always evolving. I am looking to join your company to share my expertise and passion for Information Technology with you. I am available for an interview at your convenience. Available immediately. Valid passport.

EDUCATION

MASTER'S IN INDUSTRIAL COMPUTING AND NETWORKS 2018 - 2020

Université Technology Specialist Informatics (T.S.I)

BACHELOR'S IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY 2017

Institut UNIVERS Informatique

2012 MASTER'S IN ENGINEERING COMPUTER SCIENCE

Ecole d'Ingenieur de Geneve [E.I.G]

SKILLS

- Managing a schedule and a budget
- Fullstack Developer in
 - PHP (Symfony, Laravel)
 - JavaScript/TypeScript (Next.js, React.js, NestJS, Angular, React Native, and Node.js)
 - .NET C# and its derivatives such as Blazor, Minimal API, WPF, etc.JAVA, SPRING, SPRING BOOT...
- Programmable automation & microcontrollers
- Ability to lead a team of professionals

- Organization and communication skills
- Adaptability
- Client relations
- Autonomy
- DevOps, Microsoft Azure, AWS, Terraform, Elastic Search Kibana (ELK), Unit Testing, Versioning.
- MSSQL, MySQL.
- · Proficiency in languages: French, English, and Spanish

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dec 2024 - Mar 2022 Tana, Madagascar

Project Manager for Inventory Management YHAJA MADAGASCAR

Stock Management Strategies for Feed and Cheese:

- Designed a business application [technology: DOTNETCORE C# WPF] to track product traceability.
- Trained employees to use the developed application.
- Improved the logistics calendar.
- The application manages various types of loans and debts related to transactions

2023 - 2024

Tana, Madagascar

CEO of Nossidea

 Developed the business application for Espace Santika in Madagascar using Symfony, API Platform, and React.

Mar 2022 - Jul 2021 Tana, Madagascar

Project Manager for Entrepreneurship, Bottled Water Sales YHAJA MADAGASCAR

Feasibility Study and Project Execution Preparation:

- Design project plans (objectives, budgets, schedules, resources)
- Define tasks to be completed and coordinate their execution with the team
- Manage the timeline, budget, and risks during project execution

Creation of Potable Water from a Water Source (River):

- Work with the team to create and wire the electrical control panel for motors
- Build Archimedes screw water decanter machines
- Manage communication between the different stakeholders of the project
- Anticipate risks and manage the budget during project execution

Ongoing Bottling Process:

- Prepare the setup for the conveyor and machines for the bottling process (control panel, TIA PORTAL automation, and power).
- Build a large ultraviolet filter to eliminate particles smaller than one micron.
- Research the best method to treat the water using sodium hydrochloride.

Sept. 2020 - Jan. 2023 Tana, Madagascar Lausanne, Geneva, Switzerland

Business Application Developer for Car Rental Aloc-cars, Switzerland

Project Management:

- Migrating the application to a microservice architecture using PHP, JAVA, and DotnetCore C#, Docker, load balancing, DevOps, Minimal API, etc.
- Enhancing user security by implementing JWT authentication [ASP.NET Web API DotnetCore, DAL using the Dapper framework].
- Migrating the front-end to Angular 8.
- Implementing automatic image detection (front view or profile) uploaded by the administrator using Deep Learning and image processing.
- Developing a mobile application (Xamarin) that detects failures when returning rented cars. Deep Learning is developed in Python using the Keras and TensorFlow frameworks.

2019

Tana, Madagascar

Consultant Developer YHAJA MADAGASCAR

Main Responsibilities:

- Develop the business application for cheese stock management, including logistics and IT flows (chain production without financial flows since the company does not export products abroad). The application also manages products based on customer orders.
- Monitor the milk production interface using probes and ARM microcontrollers (STM32).

2014 Douala Cameroun

Quito Ecuador

Business Application Developer for Money Transfer Cash-Xpress, Geneva - Pacoservices, Lausanne

Main Responsibilities:

- Travel to Douala (Cameroon) for 2 months, then Quito for 10 months to develop their business application for money transfer.
- Implement a single user interface with two different databases for the two companies [ASP.NET WebForms for the front end and Data Access Layer using the Dapper framework, MSSQL Server for the back end].
- Fix bugs in the application and resolve internal issues with agents and external issues with pavers.
- Develop bots to ensure secure communication between the agency application and the payer application (using SOAP Web Services, Console Application, and scheduling via a Windows Service).

INTERESTS

 Travel: Douala (Cameroon), Geneva and Lausanne (Switzerland), Quito (Ecuador).

• **Sports:** Swimming, Football, Chess.

• Music: Classical Piano, Jazz Piano.

REFERENCES

References available upon request.